<resources>
    <string name="privacy_policy_text">
        Effective Date: [2025]\n\n

        Chef\'s Delights ("us", "we", or "our") operates the Chef\'s Delights mobile application . This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information when you use our Service.\n\n

        Information Collection and Use\n\n

        While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:\n
        - Email address\n
        - Name\n
        - Phone number\n
        - Address\n
        - Usage data\n\n

        Use of Data\n\n

        We may use the collected data for various purposes:\n
        - To provide and maintain our Service\n
        - To notify you about changes to our Service\n
        - To allow you to participate in interactive features when you choose to do so\n
        - To provide customer support\n
        - To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service\n
        - To monitor the usage of our Service\n
        - To detect, prevent and address technical issues\n\n

        Data Security\n\n

        The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.\n\n

        Changes to This Privacy Policy\n\n

        We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.\n\n

        Contact Us\n\n

        If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:\n
        - By email: support@chefsdelights.com\n
        - By phone number: +1 (555) 123-4567\n
        - By mail: 123 Bhaktapur, Foodie City,Nepal
    </string>
</resources>